Guide to the Labor Publications and Printed Material Collection, "1861-2011 IBT0001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Union Publications, 1899-2013; Series 5; 6.25 Linear Feet
  - Strike Call by Window Cleaners Protective Union, Local No. 8 of the B.S.E.I.U. Amalgamated Building Service Workers Industrial Union, 1929 November; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Sugar: Honey For A Few Blood And Sweat For Many, February 1984; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan by Bethlehem Steel Corporatio; United Steelworkers of America, 1974 August 1; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Tacoma ICE Company Print, Undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - The Taft-Hartley Law from A to Z from UAW-CIO Education Department, 1951 October; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Talks With Stewards, 1966; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - The Teamster Leader, 2000-2001; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Teamster Legend's in Labor's International Hall of Fame Poster, Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - The Teamsters Union - Its Membership and Structure by Information Department, Western Conference of the Teamsters, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Technocracy from the Viewpoint of an Editor by Robert Cromie, 1933 January 18; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Tenant Farmer by Erskine Caldwell, 1935; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - There Ain't No Justice...Just Us by Workers' Rights Center, 1979 August 17; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - There's No Place Like Home If You Can Get One by Joseph Gaer, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - They Can't Run The Office Without Us: 60 Years of Clerical Work, 1985; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Thirst for Learning...a Lifetime Need by Lillie Pope, 1973 September; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - This is Your Union! by the United Steelworkers of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - To Clear the Record: AFL-CIO Executive Council Report on the Disaffiliation of the UAW by AFL-CIO Executive Council, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - To Clear the Record, 1967; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Together We Win by United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Touring Pullman, 1977; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Trade Show, April 2008; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Trade Union Africa/L'Afrique Syndical:Special Congressional Edition, 1965; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Trade Union Institute for Economic and Social Development by United Labour Congress of Nigeria in cooperation with the African-American Labour Center, May 1960; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Trade Unions in Chains by B.A. Bentum, Trade Union Congress (Ghana), December 1966; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Transport International, 2003; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Transport International, 2004; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Transport International, January - March 2006; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Transport International, April-June 2006; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Transport International, July-September 2006; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Transport International, July-September 2007; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Treacherous Passage by National Maritime Cooks and Stewards CIO Ruth Sutherland, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - The Truth About the 5th Amendment! by United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - The Truth About Unions, 1946; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Tsangas Industrial History Center, Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Two Years - A Record of Struggle and Achievement of the East Coast Seamen, 1939; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - TWUA Film Catalogue, Summer 1949; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Typographical Journal, September 1983; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Typographical Journal, June 1984; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - UAW Local 600 Facts, vol. 71, No. 3 by UAW Local 600, 2011 July - September; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - A UE Delegation Visits the Soviet Union by United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - UE Led the Way by United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE), undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - UIU Health and Welfare Fund Summary Benefits and Services History and Background, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Una Letra Aperta A Tutti I Membri Della International Longshoremen's Association by National Maritime Union of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Under Britains Heel by William Standard L., undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Underdogs vs. Upperdogs by Jim Peck, 1951; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Unemployment, 1963; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Unidos Venceremos by United Electrical, Radio, & Machine Workers of America (UE), undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Union Autonomy Plus United Action, 6 February 1946; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Union-Company Awareness Program by UAW; Chrysler Corporation, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Union Drive in the Southwest: Chicanos Strike at Farah by The San Francisco Bay Area Farah Strike Support Committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Unions in America, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Union Leadership Manual by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Union - Non Union Construction Wage Differentials, 1980; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Union Structure and Administration Constiution of International Union by United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO-CLC, 1976 September 2; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - The Union Worker's Bible by Ronald E. Fishman, 1977; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - The Union Worker's Bible, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Union Powers and Workers' Rights, 1950; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Union Wages and Hours: Motortruck Drivers and Helpers, 1 July 1952; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - A Unionist's Guide to the Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970 by The Industrial Health and Safety Project of Urban Planning Aid, 1971; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - United Glass And Ceramic Workers of North America CIO-CCL, 27 February 1956; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - United Textile Workers of America 75th Anniversary by United Textile Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1976; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Unity, 15 April 2004; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Unity, 15 April 2002; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - The Urban School Crisis by League for Industrial Democracy, United Federation of Teacher, AFL-CIO, 1966; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Regions and Regional Office Cities, undated; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Union Perspectives on New Work-Based Youth Apprenticeship Initiatives, 1992; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Upgrading Job Ladders and Such Like, 1969; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Upgrading Job Ladders and Such Like, 1969; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - UPS Teamsters, 2008; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - US Congressional And Legislative Facts, Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Victory For Democracy, 4 October 1944; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Vital Questions anf Answers Concerning National Labor Relations Board Practice by the Legal Department, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America AFL, 1954 April; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Wage-hour Conversion Table, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Wage Guidelines The Road to Austerity, March 1979; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Wartime Labor and Industry in Britain, September 26, 1942; Series 5 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - We Always Remember: A Pamphlet of Materials on the Repression of the IWW in the first Red Scare in the United States of America, 1917-1920, 1997 November; Series 5 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - We Saw Israel...a Report of A Visit by American Trade Unionists, 1954 November; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - What Workers Should Know About Automation by Eric Hass and Staphen Emery, 1957; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - The Western Federation of Miners Official Ballot, undated; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - What the Nation's Leaders Say About National Maritime Union by National Maritime Union, undated; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - What is the Teamsters Union, 1979; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - What Time Is It, America?, 1943; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - What Young People Shoudl Know About Labor Unions, 1971; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - What Will Social Security Mean To You?, 1940; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - What's Going To Happen, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - What Every Supervisor Must Know About, 1971; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - What's Wrong with Job Evaluation by Research Department International Association of Machinists, 1954; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - When Our Seamen Ship Out...by Pilot, Education and Publicity Department National Maritime Union of America, CIO, 1946 May; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Where We Stand by Albert Shanker, 1972; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Who Are the Hacks in the NMU?, 1948 January 9; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Why Unions?, 1982; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Why Child Labor Laws?, 1946; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Women and Equality by Margaret Cowl, undated; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Women Organizing the Office by the Women's Work Project, 1978; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Workers' Education Today and Tomorrow, 1933 December 8-10; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - A Worker's Guide to Contract Language by National Labor Law Center, Natinoal Lawyers Guild, undated; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Working and Fighting Together by CIO Committee to Abolish Racial Discrimination, 1943; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - The Working Mother by Alice H. Cook, 1975; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Working USA the Journal of Labor and Society by Immanuel Ness, 2005 September; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Worker- Centered Learning- A Union Guide to Basic Skills, 1999; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Working Parents Take Action, November 1987; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Writing Your Local Union History, 21 March 1984; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Working History: A Manual For Researching And Writing Labor History In Cleveland, Ohio, 1982; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Working Class Voices, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Women's Stake in Unions, 1946; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Women's Rights, Histori Sites: A Manhatten Map of Milestones, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Women and American Trade Unions, 1968; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - The World Bank, 1995; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - You Never Know! Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Insurance Department, 1954; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Your Civil Liberties - How To Protect Them, January 1940; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Your History and Membership with Local 212 - UAW by UAW, 1972 February 20; Series 5 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Your Stake In Collective Bargaining, May 1946; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - A 10-Year Record of Progress 1965-1975 by United Steelworkers of America, Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 100 Years of Struggle and Success by the AFL-CIO, 2000; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 10 Years of Trade Union - Democracy In Action, 1941-1951; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 14.B - The Hoax that Divides America, 1965; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 1944 NMU Election Year: It's Your Union by the National Maritime Union, Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 1946 NMU Election Year by the National Maritime Union, Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 1977 Steel Settlement by United Steelworkers of America, Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 100th Birthday Celebration 1998 Paul Robeson, Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 50th Anniversary IATSE, 1893-1943; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The 959 Story - Noteworthy Years, 1974; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Convention News, 2016; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Drive-Up Standards, 2016; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa Hall - Convention News, June 2016; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Hong Kong Confederation of Trade Unions newsletter, 2021; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 5)
  - The International Teamster, November 1946; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Local 70 News, 28 November 1977; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Teamster Aviation Professional - Vol. 7 Iss. 1, Undated; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Teamster Magazine, 2019-2020; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Teamster Times - Local 331, 2020; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Warehouse News, February 2016; Series 5 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 11)
- Oversize material, 1923-2000; Series 6; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Arranged chronologically
  - The Anthracite Coal Strike of 1922, 1923 April 13; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Anthracite Emergency of 1922-1923 and How it Was Handled by the United States Coal Commission, 1923 April 21; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "Black Gang News" by Pacific Coast M.F.O.W & W. Association, 193 September 3 - 17; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - The Campaign Guide: Organizing the Construction Industry, 2000; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Eighty-Eigth Convention International Typographical Union, 1946 August 17-23; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Outlaw Strikes in the Anthracite Fields by the United States Coal Commission, 1923 May 1; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Survey of Citizen CIO by the National CIO, 1944; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Summary and Recommendations as to Industrial Relations in the Anthracite Fields, 1923 June 4; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - West Coast Sailors by the Sailors Union, 1936 December 25; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 20 Questions and Answers for TWUA Stewards by the Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, undated; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 50 Golden Years, 1947; IBT0001 Series 6; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America (Flat box 38, Folder 1)
    A series of illustrations of people working on various tasks throughout history, from ancient Egypt to mid-20th century America.
  - 60 Words A Minute and What Do You Get? Clerical Workers Today by Jean Teppermen, undated; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 80 Years Young and Still Growing, 2000; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 100 Years of Struggle and Success, 2000 January; Series 6 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Labor and Union Reference Materials, IBT0001 Series 7
  - American City: Rank and File History of Minneapolis, 2005; IBT0001 Series 7 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Cards from Labor and Industry Museum, 2002; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Crossing Hoffa, 2007; IBT0001 Series 7 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - The Enemy Within, 1960; IBT0001 Series 7 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - The Fall and Rise of Jimmy Hoffa, 1972; Series 7 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Fundamentals of Human Resource Management, 2014; Series 7 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - The Gibraltar, 1988; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Haymarket Postcards from Kerr Publishing, 1986; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - History from Below, 1986; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa! Ten Angels Swearing, 1965; IBT0001 Series 7 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa The Real Story, 1975; IBT0001 Series 7 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Hoffa The Real Story, 1975; IBT0001 Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - "I heard you paint houses", 2004; IBT0001 Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Labor Rising, 2012; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Mill and Factory Survey of the Month, 1954-1955; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - One Man's Freedom, 1962; Series 7 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Strategic Human Resource Management, 1999; Series 7 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Streetfighter in the Courtroom, 1977; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Tentacles of Power, 1965; IBT0001 Series 7 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - UNION, 2015; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Various Labor Pamphlets, ?-2005; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Various Labor and Union Pamphlets, 1914-?; IBT 0001 Series 7 (Box Shared Box 34, Folder 1)